tsu.co 2015-11-07

# None

Updated: December 5, 2014

Evacuation Complete LLC operates tsū, a social networking and payment platform. This Privacy Policy explains our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information we receive through our tsū website and our official tsū mobile apps that link to this Privacy Policy. We refer to the website and apps together as the "Service". By accessing our Service, you are agreeing to the collection, use, disclosure and other handling of your information as described below. You also are agreeing to our Terms of Use.

## 1\. Information Collected From You On the Service

### Information You Submit to Us

You may provide information to us through the Service, such as the following:

  * Contact information, such as name, telephone number, and email address.
  * Profile information, such as date of birth, gender and photograph
  * Your location
  * Personal information in content you post
  * Additional information we request to verify your identity for certain Service-related activities such as receiving a payment or establishing a Verified Account (for example, completed tax forms and copies of government-issued identification documents)

### Automatically Collected Information

We and third parties may use automated means to collect information about you, your computer or other device, and your use of the Service. These automated means include cookies, Web server logs, Web beacons and JavaScript, as well as functionality that can collect data from a mobile device.

Cookies are files that websites send to your computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify your browser or to store information or settings on your device. Our Service may use HTTP cookies, HTML5 cookies, Flash cookies and other types of local storage (such as browser-based or plugin-based local storage). Your browser may tell you how to be notified when you receive certain types of cookies and how to restrict or disable certain cookies. You also may be able to delete your Flash cookies or adjust your Flash cookie settings by visiting the Adobe Flash Website Storage Settings Manager by following Adobe’s instructions [here](https://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html) (instructions vary depending on your operating system and version of Flash). Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to use all of the features of our Service.

In conjunction with the gathering of information through cookies, Web servers may log information such as your device type, operating system type, browser type, domain, and other system settings, as well as the language your system uses and the country and time zone where your device is located. The Web server logs also may record information such as the address of the Web page that referred you to our Service and the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet. They also may log information about your interaction with our Service, such as which pages you visit. To control which Web servers collect information by automated means, we may place tags on our Web pages called "Web beacons," which are files that link Web pages to particular Web servers and their cookies. We also may include Web beacons in e-mail messages. We or third parties also may send instructions to your device using JavaScript or other computer languages to store or gather the sorts of information described above and other details about your interactions with the Service.

Through our apps, we may collect information similar to the data mentioned above. We also may collect unique device identifiers (for example, advertising IDs) and other mobile-specific types of information. For example, depending on your device settings, we may collect your device’s geolocation.

When you connect an external social network account to your account on our Service, we may collect information from the external social network, such as your public profile, friend list, email address and likes and your friends' photos. Please see your external social network’s privacy policy or support documents for more information about their sharing of information with connected accounts.

## 2\. Use of Your Information

We use the information we collect to provide the Service and for other purposes, including to generate advertising-related revenue that supports the Service. Uses include:

  * To verify your identity;
  * To establish your account;
  * To create, tailor, deliver, and analyze the effectiveness of advertising and promotional material;
  * To process payments and other transactions on or with the Service;
  * To administer sweepstakes and contests;
  * To contact you for other purposes;
  * To moderate content and to try to keep the Service safe;
  * To detect, investigate or respond to security issues;
  * To analyze, customize and personalize the Service;
  * To improve the Service and to research and develop innovative features and new services
  * To safeguard our and others’ rights or property;
  * To create aggregated, anonymized or de-identified information, which we may use and disclose without restriction;
  * To investigate, prevent, or take action regarding unlawful or harmful activities, including potential threats to the physical safety of a person, potential fraud, and violations of our Terms of Use; for example, we may share your post with possible content owner in an effort to protect copyright; and
  * To administer and troubleshoot the Service.

## 3\. Sharing Your Information

We may share your information to provide the Service and for other purposes. For example, we may share your information:

  * As part of the expanding and evolving social aspects of the Service, for example: 
    * We may publish your profile information (subject to any applicable settings); your name and username; your friend list; the people you follow or those who follow you; your tree; and your likes and comments;
    * Subject to your settings, we may publish the content you post;
    * We may publish information through other sharing and publishing features on the Service;
    * We may offer a feature in which we allow anyone with your contact information (such as email address or telephone number) to find you through our search bar or through other tools we may provide, such as contact importers, even if you have not shared your contact information with them on the Service;
    * If you connect your tsū account to your account on another service (for example, to enable cross-posting), we and the other service may exchange registration info, profile info, or other details;
  * With the recipient of a payment you make on the Service;
  * At your direction (such as when you authorize a third-party app to access your tsū account);
  * With companies that perform services for us, with us, or on our behalf, including without limitation advertising and data companies, payment processors, providers of technical infrastructure and support, order fulfillment companies, content moderation companies, and e-mail service providers;
  * With our affiliates and joint marketing partners;
  * To detect and address fraud, security or technical issues;
  * Without restriction when the information is aggregated, anonymized or de-identified
  * In connection with significant corporate events (for example, we may share or disclose information we have about you in the event we sell or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets — such as in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, bankruptcy, dissolution or liquidation — or take steps in anticipation of any such event);
  * When we believe in good faith that such sharing is reasonably necessary in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding possible unlawful activities or to comply with legal process or other legal requirements (such as tax reporting); when we deem disclosure appropriate in situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, potential violations of our terms (such as our Terms of Use), or claims of violation of the rights of third parties; or when we deem disclosure appropriate to protect the rights, property and safety of us, our employees, users, or another person or entity (the disclosures described here may involve the sharing of your information with, for example, law enforcement, government agencies, courts, or other parties); and
  * In any other circumstance where we have your consent or are otherwise permitted by law to share it.

## 4\. Online Analytics, Advertising and Do-Not-Track

### Online Analytics Providers

To help us better understand your use of the Service, we may use third-party analytics on our Service, such as Google Analytics. These third parties use the sorts of technologies described in the “Automatically Collected Information” section above. The information collected by this technology will be disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers. (We also may use Google Analytics as described in the following section.) To restrict Google Analytics’ use of your information, you may install the [Google Analytics Opt-Out Browser Add-on.](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

### Advertising Technology Providers

Data about your activities on our Service may be collected by advertising technology providers for use in delivering advertising tailored to your individual interests on other websites and online services. These ad services may track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of the automated technologies described above, and they may use this information, and other information we provide them, to show you advertisements that are tailored to your individual interests and/or based on prior visits to our Service. We and third-party vendors may use first-party cookies and third-party cookies together, and other automated technologies, and in some cases additional information, (i) to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on past visits to our Service and (ii) to report how our ad impressions, other uses of ad services, and interactions with these ad impressions and ad services are related to visits to our Service.

You may visit the [Network Advertising Initiative’s Consumer Opt-Out Link](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/), the [European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance “Your Online Choices” page](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/) or the [Digital Advertising Alliance’s Consumer Opt-Out Link](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) to opt out of receiving tailored advertising based on your Internet browsing activities from companies that participate in those programs. Some of our advertising-related activities may involve the services of companies that do not participate in those programs. To opt out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising or customize Google Display Network ads, you can visit the [Google Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads) page. The opt-outs apply only to the browser in which you set them. For example, if you set the opt-out while using Firefox, but then use Chrome, the opt-out will not be active in Chrome. To opt out in Chrome, you will need to repeat the opt-out process.

The opt-outs do not block or delete cookies, or prevent the use of cookies or other technologies for purposes other than selecting ads based on your interests as inferred by your online behavior. If you opt out, data may still be collected about your web browsing activities and you will still see advertising. Ads may be delivered based on other factors, such as the content of the web page in which they are shown, or demographic information obtained through other means.

Similar data collection takes place via our apps for advertising purposes. Modern versions of Apple iOS and Android provide certain ad-related preferences that will be communicated to companies collecting data for in-app advertisements. For more information, or to use these mechanisms, consult your device settings.

### Do Not Track Disclosure

Some third parties' data collection tools or embedded content or plugins on the Service, such as videos that users post on the Service, may allow their operators to learn about your interaction with our Service, and they may combine this information with other, identifiable information they have collected about your visits to other websites or online services. These third parties may handle this information, and other information they directly collect through their technology, pursuant to their own privacy policies. We do not change our own collection of information in response to web browser "do-not-track" signals or other third-party tools that let consumers exercise choice regarding the collection of personally identifiable information. Also, we generally do not require third parties collecting information on our websites and online services to respond to these technologies.

## 5\. Your Choices, and How to Remove Your Content and Information

We offer a variety of convenient self-serve options for updating your information and indicating your preferences. From the Settings page of your account (accessible by clicking on your name on the upper right corner of tsu.co):

  * To modify your profile information, click on Profile.
  * To modify account information, click on General.
  * To adjust your connections with external social networks, click on Social Accounts.
  * To adjust privacy settlings, click on Privacy.
  * To adjust web and email notifications, click on Notifications. To adjust mobile notifications, visit the Notification section of the Settings area within your tsū mobile app.

You can also:

  * Remove a post you made: 
    * To remove your post via our website, scroll to the bottom of the post, click “More” and then click “Remove”.
    * To remove your post via our app, tap on the vertical three dots located at the bottom right of the post. A menu appears, and you can select the option to delete the post.
  * Remove a comment you made: 
    * To remove your comment via our website, click “Delete” next to the comment.
    * To remove your comment via our app, tap the comment icon in the post and then click Delete.
  * Unlike something you previously liked by clicking “Unlike”.
  * Adjust the publication settings for each post by using the options available within the post (for example, by choosing Friends Only instead of the default Public)
  * Request deletion of your tsū account as described in the next section.

The removal and deletion options may not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you posted on the Service. For example, it generally will not remove content or information that has been stored, shared or re-posted by other users and other third parties.

The law of your country you may give you additional rights to access, correct, update or delete certain personal information we hold about you.Your country may also give you additional rights to object to our processing of your personal information or to withdraw your consent to our processing of your information. You may contact us as described below to make these requests.

## 6\. Deleting Your Account

Request deletion of your tsū account by clicking here while logged in. We reserve the right to permanently erase your account from our systems immediately or at any time after we receive the request or to preserve a record of the account for some time for legitimate business purposes and as required by law. In some cases, the deletion process may take some time. Account deletion may not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information you posted on the Service.

## 7\. International Data Transfers

While Evacuation Complete LLC is headquartered in the United States, the Service may be accessed from other parts of the world. By accessing the Service, you agree to the transfer of your information to the U.S. and to any other country of our choosing. These countries have privacy laws that differ from the privacy laws of your country, but our Privacy Policy will apply regardless of the location of the data.

## 8\. Information Security

We understand the importance of the security of the information we collect, but we cannot promise that our security measures will eliminate all security risks or succeed in avoiding security breaches. When you provide information to us, you do so at your own risk. Please help to do your part by taking steps such as (1) using a strong, unique password for our Service that never has and never will be used anywhere else, (2) protecting the confidentiality of your password, and periodically changing it, (3) accessing our Service only from devices that have an up-to-date operating system and up-to-date security software, and (4) notifying us of any suspected unauthorized activity or any breach of the confidentiality of your password. If the confidentiality of your password has been breached, you also must change your password immediately via your “Settings” page on tsu.co. Taking these steps will not guarantee security but may help lower the risk or impact of certain security threats. 

## 9\. Children

The Service is not intended for use by children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect (or knowingly allow any third party to collect) personal information from persons under the age of 13. If we become aware that personal information has been collected from a person under the age of 13, we will delete this information and terminate the person’s account. If you believe that we may have collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, please contact us using the contact information below or report that user through the “report” button on their profile page.

## 10\. Third Party Links and Services

The Service contains links to third-party websites, applications and services. Your clicking on these links (including any link posted by a user), or your use of these items may result in the collection, processing or sharing of information about you. It may also result in security problems for you. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of any third parties. We do not endorse or make any representations about third parties or their websites, applications or services. The information you choose to provide to or that is collected by these third parties is not covered by our Privacy Policy.

## 11\. Changes to this Policy

We reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time for any reason, such as to reflect changes in the law, our data collection and use practices or the features of our Service, or advances in technology. We will post the updated Privacy Policy on tsu.co and indicate its effective date or the date it was posted. Please review the changes carefully. Your continued use of the Service following the effective date of the changes will mean you consent to those changes. If you do not consent to such changes, you must delete your account before the effective date by following the process described in the Deleting Your Account section of this Privacy Policy.

## 12\. Contact Us

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy or practices, please contact us as described below. To make a privacy-related report about content, you also may click on the "Report" button in the content. 

Evacuation Complete, LLC  
379 West Broadway  
New York, NY 10012
